question_data = [
{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Greenland is covered with grass and Iceland covered with ice.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"San Marino is the only country completely surrounded by another country.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The 2005 video game &quot;Call of Duty 2: Big Red One&quot; is not available on PC.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Toronto is the capital city of the North American country of Canada.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Books","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Stephen Chbosky wrote the book &#039;The Perks of Being A Wallflower&#039;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In RuneScape, one must complete the &quot;Dragon Slayer&quot; quest before equipping Rune Platelegs.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"An average human can go two weeks without water.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Nova Scotia is on the east coast of Canada.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}
]
